<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Magpie</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="help">Help?</string>
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="file_contents">File Contents</string>
    <string name="email_example">jDoe@gmail.com\nsomeones@yahoo.com</string>
    <string name="privacypolicy">Magpie application establishes a VPN connection in order to began packet capture. Once established
SMTP packets can be collected. The packets are downloaded to your internal memory by default. We as a
company do not collect any data from user during packet capture process. Additionally, the user has an option
to send captured packets to a subsequent email, the application collects the users email address.
Once user exits application email address is deleted and must be re-entered to send additional data.  </string>
    <string name="ON_OFF">Packet Capture ON/OFF</string>
    <string name="info_forAboutus">We are a group of four attending University of Montana. This is our Senior Capstone
        project in CSCI 427 Advanced Progamming II. Are interests in computer science varies. However, we all agreed that this particular project would be an
        enjoyable endeavor to partake. Magpie named because of the method behind the Magpies nest building.. sifting, searching, for shiny tidbits to
        decorate its nest. Our tidbits are network packets specifically SMTP packets. Magpie is designed as a NFAT.</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact</string>
    <string name="thanks">Special Thanks for Icons made by Freepic from www.flaticon.com </string>
    <string name="additionalInfo">Click for Additional Info\n\nSMTP - (Simple Mail Transfer Protocol)
        SMTP is a delivery protocol. Type of protocol used for sending and receiving of emails.
        .\n\nPCAP File - PCAP or Packet Capture is a data file that is generated from network analysis. These files will then
        be further processed to view contents of the file.\n\nVPN -
        Virtual private network forms a virtual network interface. This allows for its own IP address which will
        allow for access to the network packets since all networ traffic will be routed through VPN service.\n\nPacket Capture Process - When vpn is on, packets will be come accessible.
    Once accessible, access to all network is traffic is established. However, we are in search of only SMTP packets
    which will be distinguishable by its header information. Information obtained can be sender, receiver, source
    , destination, and contents of email.</string>
    <string name="magpieopen_source">Magpie Open Source</string>
    <string name="emailstart">Email Start</string>
    <string name="magpie_fakeinternaddress">https://github.com/MagpieDevs/Magpie</string>
    <string name="how_to_runMagpie">Toggle switch to on Magpie start VPN. This begins the packet capture process.
        Toggle switch on/off, to stop VPN service. This will stop packet capture process. The type of packets captured are SMTP.
        Additionally, click on menu items to see contact us, about us, info on application, and privacy policy. </string>
</resources>
